(chuckles)
Oh.
(Bernadette:)How do you drink it?
(Howard:)Oh, just put it in your
mouth and pop it like a zit.
(Bernadette:)I think I'll have a beer.
(Howard:)First take a
picture with me.
(Penny:)Why?
Well, Raj and I always
talked about learning
(Howard:)how to make cocktails like this
together, so I taught myself
(Howard:)and I'm putting this on
Instagram so he can see it
(Howard:)and feel like a turd.
Say cheese.
(Bernadette:)Is this about the space probe
he's working on without you?
(Howard:)You betcha. The very one.
(Bernadette:)Howard, you're grown men.
(Bernadette:)You guys don't have
to do everything together.
(Howard:)I know. That's why I'm
spending tonight with you.
(Bernadette:)Trying to hurt Raj's feelings.
(Howard:)With my honeybunch.
(Bernadette:)You're being childish.
(Howard:)No. He is.
(Howard:)So I have a dominant
personality.
(Howard:)We all know that.
(Bernadette:)I'm sorry. What do we know?
(Howard:)In social groupings,
(Howard:)I just naturally wind up
in charge.